

PROFILE

Hi! I'm Mark, and I love writing good, maintainable code.

I have a very technical focused background, having worked as a mechanical & robotics engineer, then a software developer.

I enjoy picking up new languages, and using them to solve new and interesting problems.

I love growing and developing a team, while working alongside them.

CONTACT

PHONE: 0439 366 884

WEBSITE:

markpendergast.net

EMAIL:

mark.pendergast@gmail.com

HOBBIES

Lego Motorbikes Geocaching PlayStation

MARK PENDERGAST

Experienced Developer

EDUCATION

Professional Scrum Master certification – Scrum.org 2021

Certificate available

Bachelor of Engineering (Robotics & Mechatronics) / Bachelor of Applied Science (Computer Science & Software Engineering) – Swinburne Uni

2004 - 2009 Graduated with honours,

WORK EXPERIENCE

Justice Connect – Lead Developer

2022 - Current

- Released a Laravel App to 10 different jurisdictions worldwide, in multiple languages. Used by almost 200,000 lawyers.
- Released a second app to many top law firms to help manage their case load
- Worked with Melbourne University to build and release AI natural language processor
- Grew and led the Innovation team, introducing best practices and significant productivity multipliers

Detector Inspector - Business Analyst

2021 - 2022

- Introduced Agile & Scrum to the Data Science team
- Led 40X speed boost on main algorithm using Python
- Achieved 35% increase on algorithm usage

No Moss Consultancy - Lead Developer

2020 - 2021

- Led dev team to introduce Vue.js portal to large Australian fintech assisted in running Scrum ceremonies
- Co-led dev team for international fintech using React

Freightmate - Founder, Lead Developer

2015 _ 2020

- Created freight management platform using JS/SQL/PHP stack
- Grew company, mentoring young developers
- Successfully integrated with large freight broker.